Hello Gas Welcome Video Stock Market
Friends ICC General
Insurance has presented its June quarter
financial results which are
in today's video friends let's
start the video so Gas No.
4500 had an income of 38 crores in the previous quarter of
52-55 crores and Arjun 22 quadrant had an
income of 3978 crores, their income quarter is in
order and there is a boom in the on and off,
if you look at the expense which has been released by the company this time then the
expense of the gas company is 300 sorry here the
expense of the company is
426 crores in the previous quarter of 3976
crores Arjun 22 godown 3600 was expanded
which quarter on quarter
expenses also increased, after this the
operating profit has been released which
if you look here is 300 crores,
last quarter number was of 1278 crores,
Arjun 22 had an operating profit of 300-16 crores in the quarter, there is a
boom in the quarter on quadrant  We are getting it, which we can see,
a good result is being seen here
but guys look here non- this
was the operating result, it was the operating result,
now we will see the non-operating result here,
so look in the non-operating result,
now there is no income but
if we look at the expense here, it was of 3.2 crores,
here the expense was in negative, there was
no expense at all, you can see here but
in the previous quarter there was an expense of 897 crores
and in the June 22 quarter there was an expense of 2279 crores,
after this now the
profit has been calculated here, net profit was
calculated of 30090 crores
in the previous quarter, Arjun 22
Cotton has a net profit of 300.49 crores,
quadran quarter we have DR here, there is a
boom in Earn Air, so here we
can see that the gas company has
presented the overall average result, DR is also of 7.94, there is
growth quarter on quarter,
Earn Air is getting DR if
we talk about the segment  It will do it like you can see here
fire, marine, health including
personal accident, which everyone can see,
which is a good result, there is a rise
in gas income here but there was a
decline in profit quarter on
quarter, so overall average
result has been seen here, so we will do more
videos here, if you have any doubt,
ask in the comment box, see you
in the next video.